https://www.linkedin.com/in/wendy-kuo-32093773/

7201 S. CUSTER RD MCKINNEY, TX 75070 (561) 273-5988

weimmod@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Self-motivated cyber security engineer with background in information security and computer science. Member of UL Cybersecurity Assurance Program (UL CAP), this certification program was created to test cyber security requirements for embedded devices and certify devices according to ANSI/CAN/UL 2900-1 standards. Experienced in penetration tests toward Android/iOS mobile application and web application.

### SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- CISSP Certified Information Systems Security Professional (ISC)<sup>2</sup>
- **CEH** Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH) (EC-Council)
- ISO 27001 Lead Auditor
- Experienced working with Video surveillance manufactures
- Experienced with examining network layer, authentication testing, authorization testing, testing for weak cryptography
- Experienced with mobile application and web application
- Experienced with ISMS and PIMS audit

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Family Leave

Dallas

May 2021 – Present

# **UL IMS-Identity Management & Security**

Shanghai

Security Engineer

May 2018 – May 2021

Member of UL Cyber security Assurance Program (CAP) team which deals in testing cyber security requirements for IOT devices and certifying the IOT devices according to ANSI/CAN/UL 2900-1 standards. Performing security tests on IOT devices that includes known vulnerability testing, malware testing, software weakness analysis, static source code and binary code analyses. The security tests include examine identity management testing, authentication testing, authorization testing, input validation testing, testing for weak cryptography, and client-site testing. Reviewing clients Product and software design documents, along with intended use documents to determine if they align with requirements. Also performing structured penetration testing based on client requirements.

- Certification: Surveillance Cameras
- UL Cybersecurity Assurance Program (CAP)
- UL 2900 Certification and IoT security testing (Video Surveillance systems)
- UL 2900 Gap Analysis and Readiness Assessment
- Sales Support: Technical support for RFI in vehicle industry.

# PriceWaterHouse Cooper

Taiwan

Senior Consultant

Sept 2015 – Apr 2018

Performing various tests on web and mobile device includes known vulnerability testing, malware testing, malformed input (Fuzzing) testing, and software weakness analysis. Working on test execution and delivered evaluation report, technical report, summary report.

- Perform Android and iOS mobile application security tests.
- Perform web application penetration tests, and technical security assessments of applications and infrastructure.
- Perform log analysis to protect sensitive organization networks, she dissected and traced users' behavior, using software named Forcepoint to detect suspicious activity, whether it is a hijacked system, rogue insider or simply a user making a mistake.
- Perform risk assessments, measuring maturity and gap analysis, ensuring compliance, advising on and implementing ISMS and PIMS
- Develop intelligent solutions to solve information security challenges for clients including Vulnerability Assessments and Social Engineering (mail contains an attachment and use macro to track the mail).
- Identify the weaknesses in a systems network, such as SAP, Oracle and TIPTOP and creating an action plan to prevent security breaches in clients' IT environment.

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Management Information Systems, National Central University Concentration in software engineering, data analysis, and security.